We are going to sonorise the street,
I don't know how long you will have the patience to stay here,
but know that you gave me an extraordinary strength and energy
and that I am very grateful for that. Glory to our ideas!
people understand perfectly that if this guy can announce to you
that he is going to do a rapid assault
it's because he has a constitution which is a permanent coup.
And the permanent coup,
Mr. Fillon will utilize it to do a social coup.
His politics, it's a social coup. It is the destruction of
government supportive health care. it is the destruction of the Work Code.
It is a social coup.
We are going to
restore retirement age at 60 (Sarcastic laughter)
How do you pay that?
Mr. Mélenchon,
retirement at 60, well, come on,
what are you doing to these people, you are promising things,
You don't know how to pay it...
Of course I do!
We found an idea.
Respect women.
What do you mean?
If you pay women
the same way you pay men,
well the additional social dues
will pay for the pension.
My name is David Chabant, I do videos on
YouTube for the past 10 years
and if I am here now it's because I have done, following a...
a...
a funny tweet, and a little bit
with the idea of a challenge,
a manga on Jean-Luc Mélenchon doing Kung-Fu.
In fact, the idea is that
the various deputees
are about to vote a raise of about 500% of their
salary... they are capable of this by the way, maybe they will even do it...
now that this video will be published, who knows
and so, Mélenchon comes in and kicks their asses.
because, I got it once and by the time I started it
I start to look at it and everything
You see, I look at something else, do other things and the people I work with, well...
they took it and said "Wait, we're gonna look at it" and then it disappeared...
The recent election of Mr. Fillon as the Chief of the Republicans Party
makes it
that someone else is needed,
do be a counter power if I may say.